Do you understand?
This is the collective
decision of House Bradley.
So that your father may stand at the
apex of the three great houses.
That's why I signed a contract
with Bruno Bradley.
Resist if you want.
If you don't care what happens
to your precious little sister.
Ow...
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
Episode 11
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Resonates with the Past
Where am I?
Howard. Howard!
Why?
Howard, open your eyes!
Howard!
This child...
Ray.
He could still make it!
Ray, stop.
Why are you stopping me?
I think you already know why.
Let's go.
Our mission isn't over.
But...
Wrap your head around it.
This is a battlefield.
Was that Ray?
Ray, do you have a moment?
I do.
You're Ray White, correct?
Yes.
I'm Maria Bradley. Rebecca's little sister.
I see.
You are a beauty,
just like your older sister.
Both your gleaming white hair and
your red eyes are very pretty.
Is something wrong?
I already heard it from Dina,
but you really are like this.
You mean Miss Sera?
Yes. She and I are friends.
That's why I asked her to have you come here.
I'm assuming this is about Miss Rebecca.
Yes.
Isn't she just perfect?
She is impeccable.
Even though we're sisters,
we couldn't be more different.
I'm constantly compared to her,
no matter what I do.
That's why I wear strange
clothes and I always run away...
from this world.
Even with me being such a failure,
my sister is nice to me.
That's why I want to help her.
Even if she didn't want me to.
Maria,
I will protect her with everything I have.
And one more thing.
Your concern for your sister shows you
have a pure and beautiful heart.
You don't need to put yourself down.
Idiot.
Why... Why?
Why am I thinking about that this much?
Because it's weird, that's why!
What was Maria even doing there?
And why was he holding...
Holding her?
I guess it's true that Ray is pretty
oblivious of his own effect on girls,
and oddly comfortable around them, so I
already had an inkling, but...!
No...
It's not my place to say
anything about that.
Shall we sleep?
You're going to stay up longer?
Yes, a bit more.
What are you reading?
Luna Ether's newest book.
Luna...
Oh, so a love story.
Not something I would have expected
from you, that's for sure.
You should read it, too.
Luna Ether is a spectacular author
who can accurately portray
the nuances of human emotions.
Our textbooks have more
than enough words for me.
So what's the story about?
It's about a girl who's said to be a demon.
Looking different than
the humans around her,
the girl lives her life
keeping herself distanced.
But one day, she meets a young man.
Since she has never interacted with humans,
she doesn't know the first
thing about human emotions.
But through her relationship
with him,
she begins to understand the human heart.
Hmm.
So the demon becomes more human, huh?
But while he develops this
relationship with the girl,
the young man becomes fascinated
by the powers she has.
The powers of a demon that a normal
human could never ever attain.
He falls into despair and
begins to avoid the girl.
Believing that the young man
will one day come back,
the girl waits for a very long time.
So that she can understand what the feelings
she has developed for him truly mean.
Well, that sounds like a depressing story.
I still haven't read to the end, either.
But I do hope the demon
girl finds happiness.
I hope so, too.
Sadness is such a bummer.
I think so, too.
Welcome home!
Master!
Miss...
Thank you, Ray.
It's fine.
Ray?
Miss Rebecca?
Ray, who are you exactly?
I am...
Was that a dream?
Miss?
Ray?
The cultural festival finally starts today.
Yes.
This is my first time doing something
like this, so I'm very excited.
Miss?
Ray, were you maybe...
in the east—
I'm sorry.
It's nothing!
I hope you enjoy your
first cultural festival.
Thank you very much.
It's going to be so much fun, huh?
It will.
Let's go find Amelia right away.
To Amelia's!
A maid cafe.
This means...!
Become super tasty!
Moe moe kyun!
Wow, it's a heart!
That's so neat!
Um, thank you very much.
Please enjoy, Miss Ariane!
Please take your time.
That reminds me.
I haven't seen Ray at all.
Maybe he's in the kitchen?
Wait, don't tell me!
I'm Lily White.
Sorry I kept you waiting.
Wow!
Is that...
Incredible!
I! Can't! Believe! It!
Is that seriously White?!
Really? I love it!
She's too cute!
I feel like a new door is opening for me.
I can't believe you!
Ow!
It's Lily!
Oh, Miss Tiana!
All right, everything is in place now.
I will execute this perfectly.
I am a pro, after all.
And a specialist!
This is so scary!
It's f-fine.
I am angry!
I guess this is it's own kind of fun.
But it is pretty lonely, too.
Everyone's having so much fun.
Don't space out.
We have a job to do.
But my naughty festival plans with Ray...
Oh, jeez.
Thank you for waiting.
Here is your super moe moe rice omelet.
Miss Maria.
Lily!
I knew they meant you with
that beautiful flower!
You're very perceptive, Miss Maria.
You praised me!
And now we cast the magic spell!
A magic spell? Not sorcery?
Become super tasty!
Encoding.
Decoding.
Processing.
Embodiment.
Moe moe moe moe scatter shot!
Miss Maria, are you all right?
Wait, I can't!
No way, it's too much!
You're too precious!
Miss Maria?
I hate to admit it, but I lost.
What do you mean?
As I thought, Ray's a terrifying girl.
I'm not really sure what's going
on, but that's pretty amazing.
So that's how a professional does it.
Amazing! So cute!
Have I wandered into a seriously
terrifying place here?
So, Miss Rebecca.
B-But...
Come on, it's the cultural festival!
You need to go have fun.
With Ray!
What's wrong?
Well... uh...
Miss?
Shall we?
I am angry! I'll curse you!
Eek!
Don't worry.
It's a very cute ghost.
Oh, you're right.
Hey, you two shouldn't be so relaxed!
Thank you so much for spending time with me.
It was my pleasure.
I'll take my leave now.
All right.
Ray!
Yes?
They're going to have fireworks
tomorrow at the end of the festival.
So I was thinking...
What is it?
No, it's nothing!
Goodbye!
Sister...
White hair. Just like mine?
Maria Bradley, may I
speak to you for a bit?
What?
At this rate, your big sister,
Rebecca Bradley,
will die.
Rebecca is going to die?!
Master, what are you saying?
Calm down, Ray.
Only if we don't do something.
You're here so that doesn't happen.
But...
Why don't I explain it?
Iceblade Sorcerer, Ray White.
Please, save my daughter. Save Rebecca.
So, Ray...
What is it?
If something's up, you can tell me.
Neither Al, nor Amelia, nor anybody
else would be bothered, you know?
Evi....
We're friends, right?
We are.
Tomorrow...
It will be time.
The Kreuz will awaken.
You do whatever you like.
So long as I get to eat...
the Iceblade, that is!
Big Sister... Big Sister...
Good morning!
Miss.
I've been waiting.
For me?
Please look after Maria.
Huh?
I'm engaged.
Soon, I will be leaving the Bradley house.
That means I'll have fewer and
fewer days to spend with Maria.
Miss...
But she avoids me anyway,
so I guess it will be fine.
She can be blunt, and she has a sharp tongue,
but she's a good kid at heart.
A very kind one.
Yes. I'm aware of that.
You don't have to worry about me anymore.
So, please be a friend to her, going forward.
Miss Rebecca...
Coming in.
You made it.
I'm sorry we kept you waiting.
Let's go, then.
Right when we're in the middle
of a fun cultural festival.
Give it up.
Stop dreaming and get ready, Dumbpink.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm already done, anyway.
Moe moe scatter shot!
Thank you so much for that.
Miss Maria?
May I ask you for a favor?
Yes, anything.
Please give me courage!
Miss?
Lord Evan?
Thank you for the lovely memory.
I didn't think you'd get her, too.
I really can't let down my guard.
Ray?
Amelia...
What is it?
I have to go.
Hang on. Ray!
What happened to Ray?
I don't know.
Everyone, listen up.
Please wake up.
Where am I?
We are going to break you now.
The party begins now.
The Iceblade.
I can't wait.
What's that?
There're so many of them.
I don't know how far I can
get with just Inside code.
Butterfly Effect?
Ray!
Are you all right?
What is going on here?
I've seen these monsters before.
Ray, you should have said something!
Everyone...
This time, it's our turn to save Ray!
What is going on?
Big Sister!
So you've come.
Maria.
Albert!
Febris Draco!
Tornado Impact!
Sparkle Web!
Elisa, we did it!
Yeah!
Butterfly Effect.
Explosion!
Your Engram is mine!
Who the hell are you?
Wouldn't you like to know?
Not a lot of prima materia, but...
Para, stop worrying about that brat.
Please head up instead.
All right, fine.
That's...
Ray, go!
We don't know what's going on,
but we'll be fine here.
Let us handle this.
Ray.
Ray!
You guys...
Thank you.
Your voice!
The name Bradley is a curse that
was cast on our bloodline.
Because of the massive bloodshed
revolving around the Kreuz
that appears once every few hundred years...
So Miss Rebecca is the Kreuz?
Right now, she is very far
away from being the Kreuz.
She can't even control
her own sorcerer's eye.
If she continues to be
unable to control her power,
Rebecca probably won't
even live to see twenty.
Maria being born as an albino was due to
the after-effects of Rebecca
being born as the Kreuz.
It might not be limited to Rebecca,
meaning there may be some sort
of effect on Maria, as well.
That's why...
That's why I...
Miss Rebecca!
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
~ Next Episode Preview ~
This is the preview of the next episode
of The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World!
Everything has converged.
Love and hatred are forming an eddy.
The glimmering Iceblade is a single
flash that rules the world.
"The Boy Who Became the World's
Strongest Sorcerer Unveils Ākāśa"!
Episode 12
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Unveils Ākāśa
I am the Iceblade Sorcerer, Ray White!